<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Newsletter on Nicolas Bontempo</title>
    <link>http://nickbom.github.io/tags/newsletter/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Newsletter on Nicolas Bontempo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 19:33:49 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://nickbom.github.io/tags/newsletter/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter - 2020/1</title>
      <link>http://nickbom.github.io/posts/2020/3newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 May 2020 19:33:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nickbom.github.io/posts/2020/3newsletter/</guid>
      <description>Extreme ownership - This TED talk, Jocko Willink shows how you can increase team performance, confiability and create a culture of self improvement by having ownership. I think that one of the best example on the software domain is the nubank speak (sobrevivendo a escala) that they show how extreme ownership can be powerfull to change the perspective of the incident and this can improve the culture of the company.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter - 2019 / 2</title>
      <link>http://nickbom.github.io/posts/2019/2-newsletter2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2019 16:33:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nickbom.github.io/posts/2019/2-newsletter2/</guid>
      <description>Starting the second semester with the right foot one new post with some interesting articles, this articles are what I&amp;rsquo;m studying right now and found interesting.
  Centralization, structuring decision making in the team - How can affect the team performance and advantages and disadvantages. In a centralized authority we have a less team interdependence, task-focused on execution, low complexity tasks, high diversity in experiences. In a decentralized, we have greater team interdependence, creativity focused tasks, high complexity tasks, low diversity in experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Newsletter - 2019 / 1</title>
      <link>http://nickbom.github.io/posts/2019/1-newsletter/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Feb 2019 16:33:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nickbom.github.io/posts/2019/1-newsletter/</guid>
      <description>This is my first newsletter. The idea was to provide some useful links to great articles that I found on the web. I expect that you appreciate. One or another is in PT-BR that is my main language, sorry for the lack of pattern.
  Great podcast that started my year, this audio provides a great experience to think about your life and in which path you are following. Café Brasil - Quando eu tiver 64</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>