<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>DevOps on Nicolas Bontempo</title>
    <link>http://nickbom.github.io/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in DevOps on Nicolas Bontempo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 22:33:49 -0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://nickbom.github.io/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy dotnet core application on app engine with github actions</title>
      <link>http://nickbom.github.io/2020/06/deploy-dotnet-core-application-on-app-engine-with-github-actions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 22:33:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nickbom.github.io/2020/06/deploy-dotnet-core-application-on-app-engine-with-github-actions/</guid>
      <description>In this tutorial, I will describe for you how to set up a Github actions workflow for your project to automatically run your tests, build your app and deploy the new code to google app engine service. At the time of this tutorial the last Dotnet core version supported was 2.1, so I created a docker file to deploy for this tutorial on Dotnet core 3.1.
1- Setup your project The first thing you need to do is create your app engine on the google cloud, for that you should go to the Google Cloud Console and create a project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Ansible</title>
      <link>http://nickbom.github.io/2020/05/getting-started-with-ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2020 22:33:49 -0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://nickbom.github.io/2020/05/getting-started-with-ansible/</guid>
      <description>Ansible is a open source tool backed by red hat since 2015, that gives you the skill to control and configure multiple server from one single location. So, instead of having to go to each server and configure them, you can create automations with Ansible to do that for you. The benefits of Ansible are that:
 Uses YAML with human readable language, that results in scripts that are simple to understand and to learn.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>